{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990374567","data":{"timestamp":" 947990374567"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" bd4e0a9e-5d89-4ebd-9645-482ef5d19fde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990386809","data":{"timestamp":" 947990386808"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 1c4a8a00-52b2-48ec-9ebc-3b8dff55b421"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lala"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LALA"," userResponse":" LALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990389428","data":{"timestamp":" 947990389428"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 1c4a8a00-52b2-48ec-9ebc-3b8dff55b421"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lala"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LALA"," userResponse":" LALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990391026","data":{"timestamp":" 947990391025"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 1c4a8a00-52b2-48ec-9ebc-3b8dff55b421"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lamba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAMBA"," userResponse":" LAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990394080","data":{"timestamp":" 947990394079"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 1c4a8a00-52b2-48ec-9ebc-3b8dff55b421"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lamba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990395674","data":{"timestamp":" 947990395674"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 1c4a8a00-52b2-48ec-9ebc-3b8dff55b421"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990398471","data":{"timestamp":" 947990398470"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 1c4a8a00-52b2-48ec-9ebc-3b8dff55b421"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990400062","data":{"timestamp":" 947990400061"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 1c4a8a00-52b2-48ec-9ebc-3b8dff55b421"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" laini"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAINI"," userResponse":" LAINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990402580","data":{"timestamp":" 947990402580"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 1c4a8a00-52b2-48ec-9ebc-3b8dff55b421"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" laini"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAINI"," userResponse":" LAINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990404203","data":{"timestamp":" 947990404203"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 1c4a8a00-52b2-48ec-9ebc-3b8dff55b421"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIMA"," userResponse":" LIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990407554","data":{"timestamp":" 947990407554"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 1c4a8a00-52b2-48ec-9ebc-3b8dff55b421"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIMA"," userResponse":" LIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990409155","data":{"timestamp":" 947990409154"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 1c4a8a00-52b2-48ec-9ebc-3b8dff55b421"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" limau"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIMAU"," userResponse":" LIMAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990412083","data":{"timestamp":" 947990412083"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 1c4a8a00-52b2-48ec-9ebc-3b8dff55b421"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" limau"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIMAU"," userResponse":" LIMAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990414102","data":{"timestamp":" 947990414100"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 1c4a8a00-52b2-48ec-9ebc-3b8dff55b421"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" limau"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990414190","data":{"timestamp":" 947990414190"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 1c4a8a00-52b2-48ec-9ebc-3b8dff55b421"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" limau"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIMAU"," userResponse":" LIMAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990488471","data":{"timestamp":" 947990488471"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8a6e17fb-c764-4730-882a-8200cfae96b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lake_baadaye-lake-wangu-nyama"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" lake"," userResponse":" nyama"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990491669","data":{"timestamp":" 947990491669"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8a6e17fb-c764-4730-882a-8200cfae96b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lake_baadaye-lake-wangu-nyama"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" lake"," userResponse":" wangu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990494502","data":{"timestamp":" 947990494502"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8a6e17fb-c764-4730-882a-8200cfae96b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lake_baadaye-lake-wangu-nyama"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" lake"," userResponse":" lake"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990588582","data":{"timestamp":" 947990588582"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8a6e17fb-c764-4730-882a-8200cfae96b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" lake_baadaye-lake-wangu-nyama"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990588666","data":{"timestamp":" 947990588666"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8a6e17fb-c764-4730-882a-8200cfae96b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_78"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivyo utakibeba bila kumwaga maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOFIKA"," userResponse":" ALIPOFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990597963","data":{"timestamp":" 947990597963"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8eab0e59-13d5-4e31-84ae-09e0c24999bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990598336","data":{"timestamp":" 947990598336"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8eab0e59-13d5-4e31-84ae-09e0c24999bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990598818","data":{"timestamp":" 947990598818"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8eab0e59-13d5-4e31-84ae-09e0c24999bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990599162","data":{"timestamp":" 947990599162"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8eab0e59-13d5-4e31-84ae-09e0c24999bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990599577","data":{"timestamp":" 947990599576"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8eab0e59-13d5-4e31-84ae-09e0c24999bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990600050","data":{"timestamp":" 947990600050"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8eab0e59-13d5-4e31-84ae-09e0c24999bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990600274","data":{"timestamp":" 947990600274"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8eab0e59-13d5-4e31-84ae-09e0c24999bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990603469","data":{"timestamp":" 947990603469"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8eab0e59-13d5-4e31-84ae-09e0c24999bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990603501","data":{"timestamp":" 947990603501"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8eab0e59-13d5-4e31-84ae-09e0c24999bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990604214","data":{"timestamp":" 947990604214"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8eab0e59-13d5-4e31-84ae-09e0c24999bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990604606","data":{"timestamp":" 947990604606"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8eab0e59-13d5-4e31-84ae-09e0c24999bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990604899","data":{"timestamp":" 947990604899"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8eab0e59-13d5-4e31-84ae-09e0c24999bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990605103","data":{"timestamp":" 947990605103"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8eab0e59-13d5-4e31-84ae-09e0c24999bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990605300","data":{"timestamp":" 947990605299"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8eab0e59-13d5-4e31-84ae-09e0c24999bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990605619","data":{"timestamp":" 947990605618"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8eab0e59-13d5-4e31-84ae-09e0c24999bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990605855","data":{"timestamp":" 947990605855"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8eab0e59-13d5-4e31-84ae-09e0c24999bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990608995","data":{"timestamp":" 947990608995"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8eab0e59-13d5-4e31-84ae-09e0c24999bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990609397","data":{"timestamp":" 947990609397"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8eab0e59-13d5-4e31-84ae-09e0c24999bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990611273","data":{"timestamp":" 947990611272"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8eab0e59-13d5-4e31-84ae-09e0c24999bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990611330","data":{"timestamp":" 947990611330"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8eab0e59-13d5-4e31-84ae-09e0c24999bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990620385","data":{"timestamp":" 947990620385"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 30e539f4-1734-4f4e-bc42-25cf41f80313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_1-4-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990672421","data":{"timestamp":" 947990672420"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 30e539f4-1734-4f4e-bc42-25cf41f80313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_7_1-4-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990680130","data":{"timestamp":" 947990680130"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 30e539f4-1734-4f4e-bc42-25cf41f80313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_7_1-4-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990687452","data":{"timestamp":" 947990687451"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 30e539f4-1734-4f4e-bc42-25cf41f80313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_7_1-4-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990695259","data":{"timestamp":" 947990695259"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 30e539f4-1734-4f4e-bc42-25cf41f80313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_7_1-4-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990703006","data":{"timestamp":" 947990703005"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 30e539f4-1734-4f4e-bc42-25cf41f80313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_7_1-4-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:L..L.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.101","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990710876","data":{"timestamp":" 947990710876"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 30e539f4-1734-4f4e-bc42-25cf41f80313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_7_1-4-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990725512","data":{"timestamp":" 947990725511"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 607953ea-1175-491c-9d2f-f4ade7e6d638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990725740","data":{"timestamp":" 947990725740"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 607953ea-1175-491c-9d2f-f4ade7e6d638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990726714","data":{"timestamp":" 947990726713"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 607953ea-1175-491c-9d2f-f4ade7e6d638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990728006","data":{"timestamp":" 947990728005"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 607953ea-1175-491c-9d2f-f4ade7e6d638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990730998","data":{"timestamp":" 947990730997"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 607953ea-1175-491c-9d2f-f4ade7e6d638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990731851","data":{"timestamp":" 947990731850"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 607953ea-1175-491c-9d2f-f4ade7e6d638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990732188","data":{"timestamp":" 947990732187"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 607953ea-1175-491c-9d2f-f4ade7e6d638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990733434","data":{"timestamp":" 947990733433"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 607953ea-1175-491c-9d2f-f4ade7e6d638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990737006","data":{"timestamp":" 947990737005"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 607953ea-1175-491c-9d2f-f4ade7e6d638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990737999","data":{"timestamp":" 947990737999"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 607953ea-1175-491c-9d2f-f4ade7e6d638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990738261","data":{"timestamp":" 947990738260"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 607953ea-1175-491c-9d2f-f4ade7e6d638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990739217","data":{"timestamp":" 947990739217"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 607953ea-1175-491c-9d2f-f4ade7e6d638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990742107","data":{"timestamp":" 947990742106"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 607953ea-1175-491c-9d2f-f4ade7e6d638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990743147","data":{"timestamp":" 947990743147"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 607953ea-1175-491c-9d2f-f4ade7e6d638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990743630","data":{"timestamp":" 947990743629"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 607953ea-1175-491c-9d2f-f4ade7e6d638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990748246","data":{"timestamp":" 947990748245"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 607953ea-1175-491c-9d2f-f4ade7e6d638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990748322","data":{"timestamp":" 947990748322"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 607953ea-1175-491c-9d2f-f4ade7e6d638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990789745","data":{"timestamp":" 947990789744"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990792101","data":{"timestamp":" 947990792100"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990793714","data":{"timestamp":" 947990793713"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990800150","data":{"timestamp":" 947990800150"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990801783","data":{"timestamp":" 947990801782"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990804177","data":{"timestamp":" 947990804176"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990805788","data":{"timestamp":" 947990805787"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990809382","data":{"timestamp":" 947990809382"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990810959","data":{"timestamp":" 947990810958"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990813062","data":{"timestamp":" 947990813062"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990814636","data":{"timestamp":" 947990814636"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990818203","data":{"timestamp":" 947990818203"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990819798","data":{"timestamp":" 947990819798"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990823009","data":{"timestamp":" 947990823008"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990824610","data":{"timestamp":" 947990824609"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990834035","data":{"timestamp":" 947990834034"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990835663","data":{"timestamp":" 947990835663"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990838017","data":{"timestamp":" 947990838016"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990839673","data":{"timestamp":" 947990839673"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990842092","data":{"timestamp":" 947990842092"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990843689","data":{"timestamp":" 947990843688"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990845892","data":{"timestamp":" 947990845892"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990847514","data":{"timestamp":" 947990847513"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990856534","data":{"timestamp":" 947990856534"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990858147","data":{"timestamp":" 947990858146"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990867109","data":{"timestamp":" 947990867108"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990868734","data":{"timestamp":" 947990868734"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990871736","data":{"timestamp":" 947990871734"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990873310","data":{"timestamp":" 947990873310"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990876388","data":{"timestamp":" 947990876388"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990877978","data":{"timestamp":" 947990877978"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990910450","data":{"timestamp":" 947990910450"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990912040","data":{"timestamp":" 947990912040"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990915401","data":{"timestamp":" 947990915401"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990916996","data":{"timestamp":" 947990916995"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990920200","data":{"timestamp":" 947990920198"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990921799","data":{"timestamp":" 947990921799"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990923620","data":{"timestamp":" 947990923619"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990925208","data":{"timestamp":" 947990925208"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990928382","data":{"timestamp":" 947990928382"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990929984","data":{"timestamp":" 947990929984"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990932197","data":{"timestamp":" 947990932197"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990933816","data":{"timestamp":" 947990933816"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990936655","data":{"timestamp":" 947990936654"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990938255","data":{"timestamp":" 947990938255"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990942314","data":{"timestamp":" 947990942314"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990944346","data":{"timestamp":" 947990944343"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947990944531","data":{"timestamp":" 947990944531"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000116_053919"," gameId":" 8cd9a279-34f5-45b9-a687-5296a82ccc3c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}